It looks like the storm
has passed, New Yorkers.
A season-high seven inches
of rain last night.
High winds and flooding in some areas...
even left some New Yorkers stranded.
City crews still working this morning.
They're trying to restore power
to several areas in the boroughs.
Good news is, today should be sunny
with highs in the low 60s...
unseasonably mild...
a real change from the relentless weather
of these past few weeks.
So get out there, enjoy the sun,
go to the park, get outside if you can...
because it's not gonna last long.
Winter storms are turning
later in the week...
Making for a severe temperature drop
over the weekend.
Could be signs for an early
and potentially long winter.
What are you doing, John?
33333333
It's been a while.
My condolences.
How are you holding up?
I keep asking, “Why her?”
There's no rhyme or reason to this life.
It's days like today
scattered among the rest.
Are you sure?
Don't blame yourself.
What are you really doing here, Marcus?
Just checkin' up on an old friend.
Good-bye, John.
- John Wick?
- Yes.
Sign here, please.
And the pen.
Sorry.
- Here you go. Good night.
- Thanks.
“John, I'm sorry l can't be there for you.
But you still need something,
someone to love.
So start with this.
Because the car doesn't count.
I love you, John.
This illness has loomed over us
for a long time...
and now that I have
found my peace, find yours.
Until that day, your best friend, Helen.”
Hey.
Daisy.
Of course.
Hey.
Come on.
I'm up. I'm up.
I'm u-I'm up.
Hey.
On. Right.
What?
We'll grab you some kibble later.
♪ Around here ain't nothin', fool,
but that money ♪
- ♪ Get money ♪
- ♪ Gotta get that money ♪
♪ Get that money, motherfucker ♪♪
Is this true?
Nice ride.
Mustang. Boss 429.
She a '70?
'69.
Huh.
- Beautiful car.
- Thanks.
- How much?
- Excuse me?
How much for the car?
She's not for sale.
Oh, I love dogs.
You have good day, sir.
All right. Come on, then.
How you doin'?
You need to go?
Uh-huh.
♪ Make it rain
Yo, make it rain ♪
♪ Ma-Ma-Ma-Make it rain ♪♪
Yo, Aurelio!
Huh? I want a new VIN number
and some clean papers.
Where'd you get that car?
Is it here?
It was.
- I asked you where the hell did you get it?
- Who gives a shit?
Iosef Tarasov nicked it.
Viggo's son.
Yeah.
Get out of my shop. Get out right now.
Did you just lose your shit, Aurelio?
Because we own you.
What did you say?
What did you say to me?
We own you.
You don't own me, punk.
I work with your father. All right?
The owner of that car,
did you kill him or what?
No.
We sure as hell fucked up his dog.
You fucked up his dog?
That's what you did?
Yeah.
That's crazy shit, man.
Oh, look at you. That's great.
You're gonna come into my shop
and pull a gun on me.
That's great, man. Come on.
Now, you kill me right now...
or you get the fuck out of my shop.
Viggo is not gonna like this.
How do you know what Viggo likes
or doesn't like?
I'll tell you somethin'
he's gonna understand.
You've got a fuckin' pair on you, old man!
I guess we'll be takin' our business
someplace else.
So what are you gonna do?
I need a ride.
Aurelio speaking.
I heard you struck my son.
- Yes, sir, I did.
- And may I ask why?
Yeah, well, because he stole
John Wick's car, sir...
and, uh, killed his dog.
Oh.
Viggo.
Yeah?
They've agreed to your terms.
It's not like you gave them
much of a choice anyway though, right?
Congratulations.
Sir?
Have you seen my son?
How was your trip, kid?
We won't be hearing
from them anytime soon.
Or ever.
That's a nice jacket.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
Ugh.
Should I go?
Nyet
- Viggo, English, please. Come on.
- Stay, goddamn it!
What did I do?
We did what you asked. No one saw shit.
I'm not talking about Atlantic City.
What then?
You mean Aurelio's?
So I stole a fucking car!
Aw, fuck, Viggo!
- Christ, Viggo.
- You stay!
It's not what you did, son,
that angers me so.
It's who you did it to.
Who? That fucking nobody?
That “fuckin' nobody”...
is John Wick.
He once was an associate of ours.
They call him Baba Yaga.
The boogeyman?
Well, John wasn't exactly the boogeyman.
He was the one you sent to kill
the fucking boogeyman.
Oh.
John is a man of focus...
commitment...
sheer will.
Something you know very little about.
I once saw him kill three men in a bar...
with a pencil.
With a fuckin'...
pencil.
Then suddenly one day he asked to leave.
It's over a woman, of course.
So I made a deal with him.
I gave him an impossible task.
A job no one could have pulled off.
The bodies he buried that day...
laid the foundation of what we are now.
And then, my son...
a few days after his wife died...
you steal his car...
and kill his fuckin' dog.
Father, I can make this right.
Oh. How do you plan that?
By finishing what I started.
Did he hear a fucking word I said?
Iosef, Iosef, listen.
John will come for you.
And you will do nothing...
because you can do nothing.
So get the fuck out of my sight.
Hello, John.
I heard about your wife, and I'm sorry.
My condolences.
It seems to be fate, or happenstance...
or just bad fuckin' luck
caused our paths to cross once again.
John?
Let us not resort to our baser instincts...
and handle this like civilized men...
to move on-
What'd he say?
Enough.
Oh, God.
Task a crew.
H-How many?
How many do you have?
Baba Yaga.
Evenin', John.
Evenin', Jimmy.
Noise complaint?
Noise complaint.
You, uh, workin' again?
No, just sortin' some stuff out.
Ah, well...